Rosalie Kaye Collection MS058
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Rosalie Kaye Collection
1927 -- 1961
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Kaye, Rosalie
MS058
1.7 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized in two series: Publications; and Ephemera.
Custodial History
This material came to the Digital Collections and Archives via Robert Ayles, Associate Director of Development.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of publications, ephemera, and three dimensional objects collected by Rosalie Kaye, Jackson College Class of 1961, during her time at Tufts.
Biographical / Historical
Rosalie Kaye (circa 1939-2005) graduated from Jackson College in 1961.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Kaye, Rosalie; Tufts University -- History; University history
- Publications, 1927 -- 1960; MS058.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains publications saved by Rosalie Kaye while she was a student.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Here is Jackson: A liberal arts college for women, 1957; MS058.001.001.00001 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - The Tuftonian, Winter, 1927; MS058.001.001.00002 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
    Volume, issue
    13, 2
  - Class of 1961 Freshman Directory, 1957; MS058.001.001.00003 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Information for new students, 1957 -- 1958; MS058.001.001.00004 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1957 -- 1958; MS058.001.001.00005 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Ivy Book with case, 1957 -- 1958; MS058.001.001.00006 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Ivy Book, 1958 -- 1959; MS058.001.001.00007 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1958 -- 1959; MS058.001.001.00008 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Faculty Pictorial Directory, 1958 -- 1959; MS058.001.001.00009 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, Announcement of Courses, 1959 -- 1960; MS058.001.001.00010 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Undergraduate Colleges, 1959; MS058.001.001.00011 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Jackson College Handbook, 1960; MS058.001.001.00012 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Jumbo Book, 1932; MS058.001.001.00019 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
    Belonged to Rosalie Kaye's father, Louis Swartz, Class of 1932 (Engineering).
  - Senior Class Day program, 1932; MS058.001.001.00020 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Commencement program, 1932-06-13; MS058.001.001.00021 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
- Ephemera and Artifacts, 1932 -- 1961; MS058.002; 1.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains ephemera and three dimensional objects saved by Rosalie Kaye while she was a student.
  - Dance Card, 1955; MS058.002.001.00013 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Dance Cards, 1956; MS058.002.001.00014 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Dance Card, 1958; MS058.002.001.00015 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Holmes poem bookmark, 1957; MS058.002.001.00016 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Diamond Mike Mayoralty Campaign booklet, 1958; MS058.002.001.00017 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Seven Songs of Tufts College, 1957; MS058.002.001.00018 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
  - Class photograph, 1932; MS058.002.001.00022 (Box MS058 Shared 1)
    Belonged to Rosalie Kaye's father, Louis Swartz, Class of 1932 (Engineering). Swartz is in the front row, fourth from left.
  - Freshman Beanie, 1957; MS058.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
    Brown and blue leather stitched together with plastic gimp.
  - Jackson-Tufts blazer, 1961; MS058.002.003.00001 (Box 3)